# Curriculum Vitae

Born 09-11-88 +45 28 91 44 41 michael@vendila.dk

# Michael Jensen

I grew up in a small town in northern Vendsyssel, Denmark, around eight years ago, I moved to Aalborg to be with my girlfriend. We now reside in a cozy house in Gug, with our 5-year-old daughter. In my leisure time, I enjoy either lifting weights, running, hiking in the Danish nature, or just immersing myself in various nerdy pursuits at home. Since childhood, I have explored nearly every facet of on-screen creativity, including 3D animation, video editing, and website coding. These days, I channel my creative energy into crafting meaningful products through a logical and practical approach.



# Job experience

#### 2022-now

### **UX** Designer

Unik System Design

Mainly focused on product discovery with product owners and other stakeholders, creating flow maps and prototypes. I am also in charge of developing a design system for our entire suite of SaaS products.

### 2018-2019

### Digital Designer

Skanva Group A/S (Vinduesgrossisten.dk)

My primary task was redesigning their entire ecommerce platform, including creating a new visual identity for them. I also acted as a product manager, working closely with the developers managing the development of the platform.

# 2017

# UX Designer (internship)

UX Designer (internship)

My internship as part of my bachelor degree. I Assisted in developing new websites for many of the different brands of the Inwido company.

# Education

# 2016-2018

# **Digital Concept Development**

UCN Sofiendalsvej

Bachelor degree with specialization in digital design and user experience.

Danish Native language

English Bilingual proficiency

### 2019-2022

### **UX** Designer

Inwido Denmark A/S

My tasks at Inwido covered the entire UX spectrum, conducting user interviews, creating customer journey maps, wireframing and designing interfaces for both websites and applications.

### 2018

#### Marketing Assistant

Inwido Denmark A/S

As a student assistant I worked on many different practical tasks, including updating websites and creating offline graphic material.

## 2014-2016

# AP in Graphic Design

UCN Sofiendalsvej

Visual communication. product development and project management.